We got two more bodies
coming out of the water.
Look like children. Aw. hell.
Roger that. Confirmed at this time.
Anyone within range of pier
2. we need fire and rescue.
We got a large craft fire...
Dozens of folks still inside.
We need to find my daughter!
Her name is Anabelle! Please!
We can't find them!
Their boat just blew up!
Please come quick!
Oh. God! Oh. God! Oh. God!
This is New Orleans pd sergeant Truitt.
I need all security teams
to check in now... all hands.
We need to know your status.
Roger that. It's bad.
Oh. man.
Look what the Navy did to us.
Turn it off.
What's the status on sonar?
Sir. the torpedo blast
ruptured several pipes
in sonar's cooling skid.
It's fixable. I think. but not quickly.
Heading into open sea with no ears
and no idea where that sub
is prowling... that's suicide.
And now New Orleans is burning.
and we can't do a damn thing about it.
Pardon me. Mr. president.
Sir. recommend using our
helo to drop passive sonobuoys
at both entry points to the canal.
Remote sonar. sir.
Acts as an early-warning system
until we get sonar back up.
That'll buy us some time.
First hit on the buoys. we
go to quiet 2. hunt that sub.
ASTAC. T.A.O... Load passive buoys.
Till then. we repair the sonar.
Let the land team do what it can do
to help the people of New Orleans.
- Aye. sir.
- Understood.
I want those buoys on board.
Get that bird in the air.
Cobra Team. give me a SITREP.
Sir. we've been working through the night.
pulling out survivors.
We got at least a couple dozen
wounded here on the beach.
We're doing what we can. sir.
Any sign of Ramsey or his people?
Negative. sir.
These people are not immune.
and they don't know what hit them.
- Stay away!
- Hang on.
No! Don't get me sick!
We're not sick. okay?
Look. you're hurt. Let me help you.
Come on.
Hey. Cletus! Don't just sit there!
Move your ass!
Washed up in the debris
were parts of a limpet mine.
Looks like it was attached
to the hull of a sailboat.
Help is on the way.
So Ramsey's people set bombs
all over the flotilla...
Just waited for us to
show up. set them off.
Continue search and rescue and report.
Sir. we're getting another broadcast.
Play it. please.
People of the surrounding
area. my name is Sean Ramsey.
I'm a lieutenant commander
in the British royal Navy.
I came here as an ally of
your United States Navy.
but that was before I learned the truth.
Shock. You breathe easy.
- Take care of her.
- About the secret lab experiments.
the release of the deadly
virus by your military.
and the subsequent government cover-up.
By now. many of you will have seen
the horrible video captured
by witnesses on the scene.
The U.S. Navy ship that
attacked New Orleans harbor
was flying the American flag.
but it doesn't represent you good people.
That ship is a key part
of a larger conspiracy
to take over this country.
and it won't be stopped until you are dead
and a new world order is established.
I know it's heartbreaking and...
"New world order"...
That's a good one. Bruv.
- Difficult to believe.
- I thought so.
But soon. you will have more evidence
of the U.S. Navy's role in
creating the deadly virus.
That is why we have
created this mobile network
to get out the truth...
Valkyrie working all right?
Broadcasting perfectly. sir.
And all the data's been
uploaded. I am here to tell you
that you are not alone.
We Brits have not forgotten
our special relationship with America...
The signal's coming from land. sir.
It's like the Bluetooth.
but somehow boosted to go long-range.
You don't need the
"deadman" app to hear it?
No... like the video of
the flotilla blowing up.
all anyone needs is to turn on their phone
to pick up the broadcast.
I'm still not sure how they're doing it.
And to the captain of the
USS Nathan James.
who has kidnapped the American president
and wreaked havoc on this great nation.
hear this.
We are coming for you.
You cannot hide from justice.
No matter where you go.
there will be no safe harbor.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.Addic7ed.Com -
I'm sorry to add to
your workload right now.
I could've gone to doc Rios. but...
I don't know.
Something weird about
getting a pregnancy checkup from the HMC.
It's a welcome distraction.
Rest assured. everything's
completely normal.
With you.anyway.
It's just... I want to
be useful to the ship
for as long as I can.
I understand the feeling.
Oh. God. I'm sorry.
Not at all.
Thank you.
For everything.
Attention on deck!
Sir.
Am I interrupting?
No. sir.
I'm back on duty in five minutes.
Very well.
How ready are you to get
your new version of the cure
out into the world?
As I mentioned before.
as soon as we safely land
in a highly populated area.
anyone carrying the new. contagious version
will be able to spread the
cure via close contact...
A handshake... Or a hug.
If each of us carries the
cure to even two people.
who then pass it on to two more people.
we'll start a chain reaction
that even Ramsey won't be able to stop.
You said you injected yourself
with the contagious cure.
Does that mean you've already
spread it around the ship?
Unfortunately not.
People who were previously
inoculated will need boosters.
We should start the process. then.
The contagious period is
only five to eight days.
according to my models. and...
With all due respect...
I believe it would be best
to wait until we're
certain we'll be on land.
Fine.
Captain.
Oh. God.
Looks like the Ramseys got
more off our secure servers
than just the location of our labs.
He's dumping all the details
of the government's
response to the outbreak.
carefully redacted to make
it look like a conspiracy.
This one caught my eye.
"Project bluenose"?
Mm. Bluenose... The Navy calls a sailor
who's crossed the arctic circle.
So that was the code name for our mission
to get the primordial virus off the ice.
Mm-hmm.
Though this is the first I'm hearing of it.
Bluenose was secret even to us.
Except. the way Ramsey tells it.
our mission wasn't to find the cure...
It was to weaponize it.
That's the problem with
top-secret missions...
They invite conspiracy theories.
He's counting on that.
sir... Mixing truth and lies
and spreading it over his network
to turn the American people against us.
And he's got help.
That's the same logo
that appeared in the video
of the New Orleans attack.
Whoever's running Valkyrie
knows what they're doing.
They've gone beyond simple text
messages from phone to phone.
This is a vast network.
The sub's running low on weaponry.
and they've missed us twice.
Now counting on civilians for help.
So we get into the network.
and we shut it down.
No. commander.
We take over the network.
use it to get our message out.
Ramsey's already told everyone
that I'm a prisoner aboard this ship.
Get me on that network.
and I'll talk directly
to the American people.
Once they hear the truth
about me. about you.
and about Sean Ramsey. we'll
turn America against him.
and we'll have the sub greatly outnumbered.
Let's go. guys. Grab that water.
Help who you can. Let's
get these people some help.
You keep eyeballing my sidearm.
I'm gonna poke your damn eyes out.
Other people are coming in
from the New Orleans flotilla.
They got water and food for the survivors.
Good. We could use the help.
Do you know if they've seen the video?
I don't think so. sir.
I haven't picked up another broadcast.
but the network is humming.
Funny thing... Signal doesn't change
no matter which way I point it.
Telling you. the signal keeps moving
depending upon who's got the closest phone.
You got people in New Orleans?
Any other immunes on your network?
No. It's my first time outside of Florida.
Signal's definitely stronger here.
It ain't me.
And stronger.
Stronger.
There.
Signal's at 100%.
Okay. people. I need a status report.
Sonar. any contacts from the sonobuoys?
No. ma'am. with the sonar
down. we're getting everything
relayed to us from the helo through ASTAC.
So far. quiet.
- Surface.
- No contacts.
Cobra Team. Viper. move
to next coordinates.
Cobra Team. roger.
Boys on land are helping us triangulate
the source of the Valkyrie signal.
I have an approximate
location of the source...
28 degrees. 33 minutes North
by 89 degrees. 22 minutes west.
No landmass. but it
could be an anchored ship.
We're gonna need a visual.
Helo's tied up with the sonobuoys.
Send the U.A.V. Nice
and high. Sweep the area.
Prep VBSS to board and take
over whatever's out there.
And get Cobra Team back to the ship.
Aye. sir.
Tower. T.A.O. Ready U.A.V.
T.A.O. tower. roger. U.A.V. on standby.
Cobra Team. Viper. render
aid and then return to Mother.
Roger that. Mother.
Just a few more wounded to look at.
then we're off the beach.
Bravo Zulu.
All right. you'll be all
right. Go take a seat.
Okay.
All right.
U.A.V. approaching point of origin.
- Sonar?
- Still no sign of the sub.
U.A.V. is eight klicks
from source of broadcast.
Zoom in on that.
Bridge. T.A.O.
We've got an oil rig at the coordinates.
I say again... an oil rig is the
source of the broadcast signal.
My fellow Americans. my
name is Jeffrey Michener.
and I am the president
of the United States.
It's not a position I asked for.
nor was I elected to this office.
The circumstances of this dreadful plague
have placed me here with
an awesome responsibility...
To help unite all survivors
and to help restore our great nation
to its former glory.
I speak to you aboard the
USS Nathan James.
a Navy ship carrying some 200 Americans
just like you... Brave men and women
who have lost their
families. their friends.
Led by Commander Tom Chandler.
these brave volunteers
left Norfolk. Virginia. six months ago
to search for the cure.
They found it.
Some of you may have heard
that the U.S. government and the military
are behind the spread of this deadly virus.
that the Navy ship is here
to spread more disease.
and that I am a prisoner on this ship.
Nothing could be further from the truth.
In fact. I was a
prisoner... Of Sean Ramsey.
the man who now claims to be your savior.
He has filled the airwaves
with lies about me.
about the ship. and about your country.
I ask you during this
time of crisis and chaos
to remember who we are as a people.
This plague has killed many.
but let's not let it divide us any longer.
We are still one nation. Join us.
Push Sean Ramsey back to the sea.
and let's restore this
great nation together.
God bless you. and God bless America.
Speech of a lifetime. Mr. President.
Let's hope it gets where it needs to go.
Sir. I will get it there or die trying.
Sir. Vulture Team has hit open water.
When they reach the oil rig.
Walker will secure the RHIB.
Once aboard the oil platform.
the snipes will secure the cap
and ensure the soundness of the facility.
The last thing the
people of New Orleans need
is the Navy causing a massive oil spill.
Agreed.
We lost visual on the rig?
Yes. sir.
The U.A.V. is en route
back to ship to refuel.
- And our radios?
- HF should work.
We'll be able to hear everything
that happens on the oil rig.
Based the signal strength
Cobra Team read on the beach.
the oil rig's got a massive antenna.
So when Lieutenant
Granderson takes control.
we'll be able to broadcast
1.000 miles in every direction.
All right. listen up.
As per the drill. Nathan
James does not broadcast.
and we need to be prepared.
As soon as the president's
speech goes wide.
that rig and everyone on it
becomes painted with a big. fat target.
Burk. stairs.
Senior Chief Lynn. as
soon as the cap's secure.
close off all the pipe valves and join us.
Aye. aye. sir.
Lieutenant Chung.
Sir?
Let's find out what makes this thing tick.
Aye. sir.
Here it is... Main power.
This looks like the
communications center. sir.
I'd say so.
Let's get you started.
Aye. sir.
Really?
What?
Green shoelaces?
Nothing.
My other ones ripped.
It's not like there's a Navy exchange store
around the corner.
You don't like them?
Just keep climbing. We'll talk later.
Get out of my head. Bivas.
No use. mate. She's got you now.
Yeah. I know.
Sir. so far. all I see
is regular telecom gear.
Nothing to run Bluetooth.
You see that antenna.
That signal is coming from here.
Keep looking.
Rig's operating on diesel power. sir.
Looks like it's been idling continuously.
Got enough fuel to last awhile.
How long?
At least a few months. sir.
Hey!
Whoa. Take it easy.
Whoa!
Take it easy.
You're outnumbered.
Don't be stupid.
You can't hold me.
My people will come for me.
Valkyrie.
Congratulations.
You found me.
All valves sealed on "A" level.
Heading down to 1 to find the main.
Outstanding.
Let's start with your name.
Don't have one.
Valerie Raymond.
Get your hands off my stuff!
Got an I.D. here from the Tulane
University engineering lab.
"Val." "Valkyrie."
Clever.
Sir. I cannot gain access to the antenna.
I'm assuming you can help with that.
After all. you're the genius
behind the "deadman" game.
Got to admit... Not what I expected.
If I hear one more "Wizard of Oz" joke...
Is that what Sean Ramsey said
the first time he saw you?
Are you like him?
Immune?
Look where I'm living.
I got myself as far away
from the sickness as possible.
No.
I helped Sean with communications
because we share a common enemy.
And that would be me?
Ramsey showed me everything
about your secret mission
to spread the virus.
And you believed him.
Well. I already knew most of the story.
Before anyone even heard
of the Egyptian flu.
I was tracking it.
I saw it jump to phase 6 overnight.
and I saw the government do nothing.
So I created Valkyrie
to help expose the truth behind the plague.
The truth?
Well. shit.
You got it all figured out.
But you forgot the most important part
of the conspiracy...
The only way we were able
to spread the flu so quickly.
The aliens.
From planet batshit crazy.
They were sneezing all over the place.
That's what you people always do.
When alternative history gains traction.
"just another conspiracy nut."
Right? "Whack job."
I got my masters in computer science
from M.I.T. at 21.
my PHD in engineering
physics from Tulane at 25.
Valkyrie. the network I
created to get out the truth.
has 6 million untraceable
subscribers worldwide.
"Had."
What?
"Had 6 million."
Most of them are probably dead by now.
The rest will die very soon.
We came home with a vaccine
and a cure for those
who were still infected.
It's on our ship.
Ramsey wants to sink us
and let the virus wipe out the rest of you
so his master race can rule the word.
And you think I'm the whack job?
It's the truth.
Look.
You're obviously a
clever and resilient woman
to survive out here as long as you have.
and you've built an impressive network.
You just backed the wrong horse.
Help me play this message.
Listen for yourself.
The truth is in here.
Sir. U.A.V. Needs another 30 minutes
before we can send her back
to the rig for a visual.
Okay.
Damn it.
Need a hand. Chief?
Ma'am. there's a secondary
valve over there behind you.
Don't call me "ma'am."
Lieutenant Granderson. how we doing?
There's clearly a component missing...
The device used to control
the Bluetooth booster.
Without it. we can't
access the Valkyrie network.
Lieutenant Chung.
Shut down the rig.
If we can't use the network. no one will.
Mr. Chung. shut her down!
Yes. sir.
Lieutenant Granderson...
Tear it all out.
Yes. sir.
What the hell is that?
Hey. quick! Grab the shot!
It's a Navy ship. turning!
You'll be all right.
Hey. did you see that?
All right. All right. you're gonna be okay.
Looks good as new. my man.
Hey! Hey!
Did you see that video before it cut out?
Them guys is Navy. Them's
the one that did it.
They're the ones that blew up New Orleans.
- Check out their boat.
- Hey. heads up. Heads up.
Those guys are Navy. That guy.
A-and check out their boat.
Uh. you... you see the video?
T-t-those guys are Navy.
They're getting away!
Everybody. just take a
breath. We're here to help.
Navy had nothing to do with that attack.
Let's just take it easy.
Let's get a move on.
Green. fire in the air if you have to.
None of these idiots need to die today.
Miller. let's go! I need cover!
Viper. this is Cobra.
Under fire from civilians.
We're on the move.
I say again. these people are not immunes!
Search and rescue
aborted! We're on the move!
Come on!
Go!
Aah!
You okay?
Can't believe they shot me in the ass!
Go. go. go. go!
See that?
I got it.
We got an unidentified civilian watercraft
half a mile. approaching with speed.
RPG! RPG!
What was that? You hear that?
- Was that the sub?
- No. sir. it's coming from the rig.
Sonobuoys are picking up an explosion.
Damn.
I've lost visual on the
boat. I've got no target.
I got him. He's circling around.
Send the helo.
X.O.. recommend sending
Cobra Team on their RHIB.
- Send them both.
- Yes. sir.
ASTAC. T.A.O...
Cobra Team. Mother. Head
to Vulture Team whisky.
They are under attack.
Roger that. We'll be there in five mikes.
Burk. Walker...
Secure the RHIB.
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant!
Are you okay?
Are you okay?!
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Walker's K.I.A.
The RHIB's fubar.
We're gonna need another way off.
Vulture Team. this is Sabrehawk One.
Oil rig AO in sight. Expect
a one-minute ETA. Over.
All teams. Sabrehawk inbound.
Exit up toward the helo deck.
Move! We got to move!
We got to... we got to
go up to the helipad.
Up this ladder. Come on.
You got this. Lieutenant. Come on.
RPG incoming!
Chung!
Ravit?
Lynn's gone.
There's a natural-gas leak.
We've got to close the valves.
How we gonna get off this rig?
We can't just bail.
There's about a 100-foot
drop into the water.
Help me with this wheel!
He's out of my range. I can't hit him.
Aw. come on.
Yeah!
Viper leader. Sabrehawk One.
Enemy threat has been eliminated.
We're going for green deck. Over.
Valves not working!
Gas is still coming out!
Sabrehawk. stand down. Red deck. Red deck.
Do not land.
We got a gas leak. Hold for landing orders.
Roger that. Sabrehawk One
will maintain holding pattern.
Come on!
Climb! I think it's broken.
Hold on!
Where the hell's it coming from?
Aw. man.
I checked all these. They're sealed tight.
Shh!
Over there.
Aah!
Leave it! Come on!
This whole rig's about to
blow! We got to get out of here!
Come on!
Come on. Chung!
Don't stop!
It's not a leak.
It's the main valve.
Viper Tower. Sabrehawk
One on 1/4-mile climb.
Request green deck.
We've got several injured onboard.
Sabrehawk One. Viper Tower.
Cleared for green deck.
EVPs standing by.
Out of my way! Out of my way!
Over here!
I got him! I got him!
Oh. my God.
- What the...
- His left pupil's not good.
Pulse is erratic.
I need a Philadelphia
collar. and I need it stat.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Doc. I'm fine.
Tex! Jesus. What happened?
Shot in the hip.
It's just the backside. I'll be fine.
Over here. Over here. Thanks. brother.
Captain. you okay?
I'm fine. Burk's burned pretty bad.
All right. let's get him in
here. Let's get him on the bed.
Ravit!
She's okay. She's okay.
Let's get you down. Go.
Holy shit.
- You all right?
- Went right through. Yeah.
Rig was a ball of fire.
Lucky anyone survived.
Go. go. go!
Keep breathing. Keep breathing. Ravit.
Get a liter of ringers in him.
- Whoa. whoa!
- Get down. Get down.
What are her injuries?
I-I-I don't know.
S-s-she-she's not responding.
Ravit.
Can you hear me?
Start a line. We might need to intubate.
Left pupil's blown. It's fixed and dilated.
His brain is bleeding.
We need to get something under
his head and shoulders now.
Hang in there. It's Garnett.
Diuretic and steroids... now! Go. go. go!
Stay with us. Just stay with us.
Just hold on. Okay?
It's okay.
Just... Just hang on. Andy.
Come on.
Hang on. Andy.
Hang on.
N-n-n-n-no.
No.
He saved my life.
Sir.
Walker and Lynn were the first to. uh...
We were unable to recover Lynn's body. sir.
I'm sorry.
You sure the people shooting at you
- were regular Americans. not immunes?
- Yes. sir.
They were afraid of the virus
until they became afraid of us.
Those RPGs came from
a civilian vessel. too.
And we sank them. which means Ramsey got us
to kill our own people... For real.
Eng.
Walker.
That rig was a ball of fire.
Eng.
I'm sorry.
Sir. you're hurt.
Dr. Scott! Dr. Scott!
Put a pillow under his head.
Looks like a shrapnel hit.
He's bleeding internally.
Somebody get a board... Now!
Valkyrie's not down. It's gone.
It's been destroyed.
The Navy?
Nope... By some regular Americans.
What do you mean. "regular Americans"?
Not immunes.
A bunch of Joe six-packs got riled up
by the video of the ship
blowing up the flotilla.
They spotted some of
the Navy folk on the rig.
and they blew it to kingdom come.
Did you hear me?
The network's gone. Sean.
But the message is out there.
My people have heard the siren call.
See this?
Come here.
My manifesto.
I'm putting all my
thoughts down in writing.
We need to get a copy of this to MacDowell
and our people in Florida.
You're in here. too. you know.
You and me... The brothers.
We're like Moses and Aaron.
The people are following us.
and the seas are parting at our feet.
Mum would be so proud.
She always said we were born
to bring good into the world.
Didn't she. Ned?
Yeah.
She was right.
Look at us now.
That's right.
He's stable.
I was able to remove some metal fragments.
but I won't know if I've got them all
until I do the ultrasound.
How long will he be out?
It's hard to tell.
All right. let's roll her.
Let me check her dressing.
Stay at her side.
Back slowly down. Let's go.
Here we go.
Easy. Easy. Easy.
I...
I-I...
Can't feel my legs.
That's 'cause they got
them wrapped so tight.
So you won't be jumping around.
You're a terrible liar.
That's why you suck at poker.
Naw. man. you're. uh...
You're all good.
You know. just a couple of scratches.
I told you you're a
mean operator for a girl.
I can kick your ass.
No doubt.
Everybody else okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah?
Everybody's good.
Good.
Ravit.
Ravit. come on. girl.
Breathe.
Everybody okay?
Yeah.
Hey. Everybody's all good.
It's all good.
Schma Yisrael...
Adonai Eloheinu...
Ravit.
Ad-adonai Echad.
Hey.
Baruch...
Ravit.
Ow.
Yeah. that's the spot.
Just trying to keep you
from bleeding to death.
I do still know how to
use my powers for good.
Ravit?
I lost four sailors.
Four more.
Well. we thought you
might've been the fifth.
It was touch-and-go
there for a while.
Still gonna need to operate and
remove this souvenir I
found behind your liver.
That can wait.
Actually. it can't.
The shrapnel can move and cut you.
I'm not going under... Not now.
Stubborn as ever.
Says the pot to the kettle.
Rachel.
Thank you.
We've taken our share of
hits these past few weeks...
Suffered painful losses.
Sometimes. it feels like
more than we can bear.
Yet. here we gather. united.
Shipmates.
Every time we're called.
we answer. "here I am."
We answer knowing that the world.
survival of our species
depends on our actions here at sea
and fullaware that we
answer at our own peril.
And still we answer. "here I am."
I'm not gonna put a silver
lining around our pain.
Today. we grieve and
we remember our fallen.
and we thank them for their
service to us and to mankind.
Yes.
Today we grieve. but
tomorrow. we do press on.
We continue to answer
the call. "here I am."
You could've run away
or saved your own people.
But you ran back for me.
Wasn't all out of the goodness of my heart.
We need you.
I'm a little. um...
I-I thought I knew what was going on.
There's still a lot I don't know.
I wanted you to be here
so you could see who we are.
Whatever was so important
in that bag of yours...
Can it help us?
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org